We've arrived!
I was very worried when I heard on the news yesterday that it was the heaviest rainfall in 100 years, but it's sunny now.
But it's sunny now.
It's cloudy but not raining, so I'm lucky.
I'm going to have a good time!
etcetera
I'm scared
I live here and I have one hand
It's slow
rubster bisque vibes mi
So, I'm going to try some.
It's cool, right?
I'll have some
Delicious
It's very rich
Well, it worked well!
This is Pappa Roasted Chicken Bing!
Since this is a lobster restaurant
I ordered a variety of dishes!
Delicious!
So soft and easy to eat!
I'm going to eat it!
Which one of these did you try once?
I don't know how to eat this for the first time!
How do you eat this?
Which way should I try this once?
I'm a mayonnaise lover, so I love this!
Delicious!
Shrimps!
This one.
Lobster puri puri
Satanlagi's.
I was asked to clean up the festivities, so I'm going in.
I ate paper, goat.
It's delicious, but I got it warmed up.
He said come on in.
Woah.
Nice salt.
This is Yosasimil bread.
I think I'll do something else after this.
I've been playing all day.
But it's time to go home.
I'm at Naha airport now.
I haven't had Okinawan soba or regular soba
I'm going to go to a restaurant in Naha Airport in Okinawa.
I'm going to enjoy Okinawa soba at a restaurant in Naha airport
I'm going to enjoy Okinawan Soba at a restaurant in Okinawa Naha Airport.
Bon appétit!
How long has it been? It's been a while since the last time I had Okinawan soba!
Gentle taste!
This is pickled pepper.
It's a very nice pickle.
My face turned red.
I can't do it. Maybe I can't, but just a little.
I'll just put a little and enjoy it.
Just a little.
Is this okay? I'll forget what it tastes like.
It smells like chili peppers and bubbles.
I only put a little bit, but it's really hot.
But there's a kind of stiffness to it.
If you like it, you'll like it.
Yo might like it a lot.
I'm going to enjoy the rest of my time
I'm going to enjoy the rest of the time.
Now that we're done eating.
I'm going to go back to the souvenir shop.
I'm going home.
Misaki gave me
Misaki asked me for an instant
I'm thinking of buying some instant soak soak
I'm thinking of buying it.
This is for two people.
But this looks so good
Somehow.
It's delicious.
I was kind of drawn to this when I saw it.
But it's for 4 servings, so you can eat it 4 times.
These are fresh noodles.
Oh, here.
It looks like it also comes with some island chili peppers.
I'll take this one. I'll take this one.
This is Misaki.
We have an important rehearsal tomorrow.
I'm going home.
Tomorrow is the most important rehearsal of all.
I'm going to do my best.
Okinawa Collection was fun!
What time did we leave?
I don't know.
Ten minutes ago.
I'm taking a carefree video.
10 minutes ago. Less than 10 minutes.
Let's hurry up.